

Over 14 years of web design experience including: strategy, research, brand building, web development, and content creation. I work closely with clients, IT, and development/marketing teams to ensure an engaging, useful, and rewarding user experience.

Skills

- Illustrator
- Photoshop
- InDesign
- After Effects
- Graphic Design
- UX/UI
- Web Development
- Google Tag Manager
- GA4
- CSS/HTML
- JavaScript
- Drupal
- Slate
- Wordpress
- Marketing Cloud
- Email Design
- Git

2021

Salesforce

Education

Digital Arts, BFA **Bowling Green State** University - 2011 Google Analytics and Data Studio Certified -

Experience

Web Developer and Designer

40 hr/wk, 2013 - Current

Wright State University

My roles include: UX design, wire-framing, brand development, web development, video editing, animation, analytics reporting, Slate portals and reporting, Drupal theme development, Salesforce, and email design.

Web Developer and Designer

15 hr/wk, 2011 - 2014

Enormous Pi

Working closely with clients I helped create and develop websites on a variety of CMS platforms, as well as advertisement development, email, content strategy, video, and photo editing.

Graphic Designer

20 hr/wk, 2011 - 2013

Collegiate Connections

I created custom designs in Illustrator and used a CAD-CUT plotter machine to cut and then press the designs onto various apparel.

Graphic Design intern

25 hr/wk, 2008 - 2009

Shirts, Signs, and Designs

I took orders from clients and worked with a team of designers to create silk screen templates to process large orders of wearables.

References available upon request